<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-09-26T01:22:45+07:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">MailSwami.</title><subtitle>No more deliverability issues for you. Our AI engine positively interacts with your emails to increase your sender reputation, so you never land in the spam folder.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to Warm Up Your Cold Email List and Increase Deliverability</title><link href="/article/news/how-to-warmup-your-cold-email-list.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Warm Up Your Cold Email List and Increase Deliverability" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/news/how-to-warmup-your-cold-email-list</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/news/how-to-warmup-your-cold-email-list.html">&lt;p&gt;Introduction: Why Cold Emails Fail &amp;amp; The Dos and Don’ts of Sending an Effective Cold Email&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;keywords: warm up your cold email list, cold email automation software, email marketing software&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s always hard sending an email to someone you don’t know, but the task becomes even harder when the person is not expecting it. That’s why cold emails fail. They are not sent at the right time or they are sent to people who are not interested in your offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s difficult to come up with an effective cold email list that includes people who would be interested in your offer or service, but luckily there are tools that can do it for you. You should find a software that automates this process, which will free up your time and allow you to send more emails without spending too much time on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold emails are still effective if they are well written and if they contain offers that people would want to take advantage of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay Away From These 10 Common Mistakes With Your Cold Email Campaigns
keywords: cold email mistakes, cold email automation, send personalized emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people don’t know how to create a cold email campaign, and this is why they make the mistakes that we will discuss in this section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We should avoid these 10 common mistakes with your cold email campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Having no clear goal: This is the most important thing when sending emails, and if you don’t have one, you are most likely wasting your time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Not sending personalized emails: It is always better to send personalized emails because it makes it easier for the recipient to open your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Sending too many emails at once: You should only send an email every 3 days or so because this will increase your click-through rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Not following up on unanswered emails: If you are not getting any replies after a few days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6 Tips for Emails That Are Guaranteed To Get Responses
keywords: warm up your cold email list, best practices for sending emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the rise of social media, cold emails have become increasingly less common in business communication. But when used correctly, they can be an effective way to introduce yourself and your company to potential customers. Here are some tips for optimizing your email outreach:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pick the right time of day: Emails seem more urgent in the morning and evening, so you’ll get a better response rate if you email people around those times.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Add a personal touch: Make it clear you’ve read their profile by mentioning something from it in your first sentence or two.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep your subject line concise: People will be more likely to open your email if they know what it is about from just reading the title of it, so don’t make them guess!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: The Benefits of Using Cold Email Automation Tools
The benefits of using a cold email automation tool are many. Whether you want to find new prospects, follow up with potential buyers, or keep contact with past customers, the right cold email automation tool can help you out. Here are some of the top reasons why you should use a cold email automation tool:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) It saves time and energy: There is no need to chase after potential buyers and send them one-by-one emails manually. The right software will do it for you and save your time and energy. 2) It improves sales: You can engage with your prospects more easily and encourage them to buy from you by sending them personalized messages which will improve your sales. 3) It’s easy to use: Cold email automation tools make it easier for non-technical people to manage their&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html">Introduction: Why Cold Emails Fail &amp;amp; The Dos and Don’ts of Sending an Effective Cold Email</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications</title><link href="/article/test/long-term-profit-with-good-email-communications.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/test/long-term-profit-with-good-email-communications</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/test/long-term-profit-with-good-email-communications.html">&lt;p&gt;The Complete Guide to Creating a Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introduction: What is Good E-mail Communication and How Can it Help Your Business?
keywords: email communication, email etiquette, how to write an email&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E-mail is the most used tool for communication in our society. It’s easy to use, especially if you have an accepted template to follow. One of the most important things to keep in mind when composing an email is that it should be clear and concise. There are a few spelling mistakes to avoid when writing an e-mail because they might cause confusion and result in your message being ignored by the receiver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/custom-image.png&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this section, we will cover different aspects of good e-mail communication and how it can help your business. We will also provide examples of bad email etiquette so that people can avoid them when composing their own emails, which would result in a higher response rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to Write Effective E-mails that Drive Conversions
keywords: how to write an effective email, how to open an email, what are the best types of emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An email is the way we convey messages to our audience. Every day, we receive emails from various sources, such as banks, retailers, and even social media sites. You may be surprised to know that the average person will spend over 80 hours reading and responding to emails this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want your messages to stand out in a crowded inbox, then it is important that you write an effective email that drives conversions. To help you do this, here are some best practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Open with a strong subject line&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use an appropriate greeting - Keep your messages short and concise&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Include a call to action&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject Line Strategies for Captivating your Readers Attention
keywords: subject line strategy, subject line tips, best practices for subject lines&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject line strategies are the first thing you see when you open your email inbox. It can make or break your email or conversion goals. A captivating subject line provides a glimpse of what’s inside and makes the reader curious to read more. But, how do we write those captivating lines?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best practices for subject lines are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Incorporate emotion in your subject line to grab the readers attention - Use action-oriented words to make readers want to take an action&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make it clear what they can expect from your email by using declarative statements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5 Tips for Writing Better Emails &amp;amp; Creating a Great Online Presence
keywords: tips for writing better emails, writing great emails online, 10 tips on writing good emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emails are a vital part of the modern office, and there are a few tips that you can follow to make sure that they’re written the best way possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep email communications simple&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use correct grammar and spelling&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Be concise&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Include a signature at the end of every email&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Proofread before sending&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: The Benefits of Good E-mail Communication and Why You Should Invest Time in It
In this section, we will discuss the benefits of good email communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email is one of the most common forms of communication from businesses from all over the world. There are many ways to use email to communicate with customers and employees, but a lot of people still don’t know how to do it properly or at a minimum they don’t know how to make sure that their emails are being read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This can be a huge problem for businesses because if their emails aren’t being read then they won’t have any new opportunities for customer interaction or for promotion. In order to be successful in communicating with customers through email, there are four tips that you should keep in mind: 1) Use Titles 2) Proofread Before Sending 3) Be&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="test" /><summary type="html">The Complete Guide to Creating a Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications.</summary></entry></feed>