<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-11-26T16:31:19+07:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">MailSwami.</title><subtitle>No more deliverability issues for you. Our AI engine positively interacts with your emails to increase your sender reputation, so you never land in the spam folder.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to Prepare an Email Account for Cold Email Sending</title><link href="/article/news/10-How-to-Prepare-an-Email-Account-for-Cold-Email-Sending.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Prepare an Email Account for Cold Email Sending" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/news/10-How-to-Prepare-an-Email-Account-for-Cold-Email-Sending</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/news/10-How-to-Prepare-an-Email-Account-for-Cold-Email-Sending.html">&lt;p&gt;How to Prepare an Email Account for Cold Email Sending&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refresh Your Email Account
When conducting a cold email campaign, email deliverability is critical. According to ReturnPath’s analysis, more than 20% of emails never make it to the inbox. At SalesHandy, we frequently see fresh email accounts used for cold email campaigns being stopped as soon as the campaign begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue is that the new email accounts are not being warmed up. With Google’s spam change in January 2019, it’s becoming more difficult to enter the inbox, as the majority of emails are now designated as spam. To avoid this, it is critical to exactly warm up your new email account before engaging in serious cold email outreach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog, I’ll describe how to warm up an email account prior to sending cold emails, ensuring that your message reaches the inbox rather than the SPAM folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is a “Warm-up” email?
The email warm up process is used to establish a fresh email account’s reputation and boost the email sending limit. The warm-up procedure entails sending emails from a new email account, beginning with a small number and gradually growing each day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a user establishes a new email account, the email service provider limits the user’s daily email sending. However, a new account will be unable to use it entirely. For instance, Google offers 2000 emails a day with a G Suite subscription. However, from day one, you are not permitted to transfer it all; you are given a reduced restriction. To fully utilize it, you must first establish a positive reputation, which may be accomplished through email warm-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally, it should take between 8 and 12 weeks to achieve optimum deliverability. The email is prepared more quickly depending on the volume of emails and the level of participation during the warming process. If the recipient involvement level is too low, the email warming may take longer than planned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is Email Warming Critical?
Email warming is a process that must be followed in order to establish a reputation and increase delivery rates. It is critical to ensure emails land in inboxes when planning a large volume cold email campaign with a fresh account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first step in a cold email campaign is to reach the recipient’s mailbox. Once there, having a positive engagement can help you develop a more meaningful relationship. If the email is thoroughly warmed up prior to being sent cold, it will bypass the spam filter, arrive in the inbox, and have a better open rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without further ado, let’s dig in and learn how to warm up an email account before sending cold emails in order to optimize your email account’s efficiency, sender reputation, and email deliverability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to Prepare an Email Account Prior to Sending a Cold Email&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Verify Your Account
The first step in creating a new email account is account authentication. Authentication protects your account from SPAM filters and ensures that your emails get in the inbox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are four critical components to email authentication:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SPF SPF (Sender Policy Framework) is an authentication approach that establishes a record in your DNS (Domain Name System) that identifies all the servers permitted to send emails on behalf of a domain. When the recipient’s ESP detects SPF Authentication on the sender’s side, it gives the sender’s domain a clean bill of health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DKIM DKIM (Domain Keys Identified Mail) is an authentication method that associates your domain with a digital signature, preventing email spoofing and ensuring that your email reaches the intended recipient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DMARC DMARC (Domain-based Message Authentication, Reporting, and Conformance) records to use your SPF and DKIM records to reassure the recipient’s email service provider (ESP) that the email is not the result of deceptive activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personalized Domain
By including a custom domain in your emails, you may increase the authenticity of your links and documents. This requires both the sender and his ESP to verify the authenticity of the links and documents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are SPF and DKIM Records and How to Configure Them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Send Customized Emails
The email warming method begins with manually sending emails to friends and coworkers in order to initiate a conversation. To begin, you should send ten to twenty separate emails from your new email account. Assure that the initial emails have constant engagement, as this will aid in increasing the volume of the emails. As the volume of interaction increases, your email service provider gains confidence in your authenticity and progressively prepares your email account for email campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ensure that you are sending emails to a variety of email services during this manual procedure, including Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook, iCloud, Godaddy, Zoho, Aol, Exchange, and Yandex. This will assist you in establishing a positive reputation with all major email service providers’ spam filters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: When using the manual approach, use a personalized subject line to ensure a better response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keep Conversation Threads Going
Email accounts are not just for sending messages; they should also receive responses. To maximize deliverability, it is critical to create engagement in your warm up emails. Therefore, initiate the dialogue by sending emails from your old accounts and responding to them from the new one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, having some regular interactions is critical, as this is an ongoing process that lasts between 8 and 12 weeks. Therefore, if possible, incorporate your new email address into your website’s contact form and promptly respond to inbound emails to increase your conversation rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This straightforward procedure demonstrates to the email service provider that your email actions are genuine. The continuous email dialogue progressively builds your email sending quota and qualifies your account for mass emailing, such as sending 1000s of emails at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Register for Newsletters
If you work in sales, marketing, recruitment, or any other industry, you’re likely to receive weekly emails from a variety of publications. Subscribing to a minimum of 10-15 newsletters is a good start. Each newsletter requires confirmation; thus, return to your mailbox and complete each subscription. It will authenticate your account and boost your email inbox’s capacity. Receiving emails on a consistent basis is just as critical as sending emails to warm up your fresh email account.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Preserve a time difference between two consecutive emails
Each email service provider uses a unique algorithm to verify the delivery and receipt of emails. Therefore, demonstrate to those algorithms that you are not a robot by avoiding sending too many emails at once. If you send a large number of emails in a short period of time, this will have an effect on your domain’s reputation.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, the best method to avoid this is to maintain a significant time difference between two emails while warming up your new account. Avoid sending an excessive number of emails in a single session; this activity triggers spam filters, which may result in your account being temporarily or permanently blocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a Customized Test Campaign (Using SalesHandy)
After 12 weeks of human warming, SalesHandy will ready your account for automated email campaigns. Nonetheless, it’s prudent to begin small and uncomplicated. Begin with a modest list of 20-30 reliable receivers, supplemented by friends and coworkers to ensure a response.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customize Your Email
When your primary objective is to warm up your email account, you must convince your receivers to open and respond to your email. Personalizing your email will suffice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create as personalized an email as possible using SalesHandy Mail Merge. Additionally, design a customized subject line to get the highest open rate. The tailored message is crucial to eliciting responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;warm-up-email-account-merge-tags
FOR FREE, SEND YOUR FIRST PERSONALIZED EMAIL CAMPAIGN–TRY SALESHANDY
Attempt to Avoid Spammy Content
By including spam in your emails, you increase your account’s vulnerability to SPAM filters. Avoid utilizing terms such as FREE, GRAB, 50%, etc. in your emails, as these will draw the attention of SPAM filters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avoid sending anything that will have a negative impact on your sender’s reputation. To ensure the best delivery, keep the information clean, straightforward, and plain, with a limited amount of links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Include an Unsubscribe Link
Even if you’re sending a test email to a tiny list, it’s a good idea to include an unsubscribe link in the email. While you’re warming up your email account, you should eliminate any potential of the recipient spamming you. Even one spam report against a newly created account might have a detrimental effect on your reputation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By including an unsubscribe link in your emails, you provide your receivers the option of receiving your emails or not. This function not only delights your recipients, but also protects your emails from SPAM filters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Most Effective Bonus Practices
Adhering to the best measures outlined above for warming up an email account prior to sending cold emails can assist you in activating your account’s vast list of cold email campaigns. I’ve included some additional bonus ideas below that can assist you in maintaining your sender reputation and email deliverability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Write as a genuine human being would.
Utilize restricted links in your email content and choose an email service provider intelligently based on your requirements
Utilize a restricted number of media files, such as photographs, movies, and GIFs.
Steer clear of automation during email warmups.
Utilize an email campaign solution such as SalesHandy to ensure that your cold email campaigns are sent in the most effective manner possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Final Remarks
The entire system is designed to weed out spammy stuff. Adhering to best practices demonstrates to algorithms that you are a genuine human being, not a spammer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, and perhaps most importantly, remember that it is easier to develop a favorable reputation as a sender than it is to improve the reputation of a spammer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html">How to Prepare an Email Account for Cold Email Sending</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Tips To Improve Your Cold Emails</title><link href="/article/news/10-tips-to-improve-your-cold-email.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Tips To Improve Your Cold Emails" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/news/10-tips-to-improve-your-cold-email</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/news/10-tips-to-improve-your-cold-email.html">&lt;p&gt;Rather than cold-contacting people for their business, think out how to give value to their life first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;1-make-your-emails-more-inclusive&quot;&gt;1 Make Your Emails More Inclusive&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than one cold outreach email has failed because a marketer misidentified a prospect: Getting some aspect of your prospects wrong, no matter how fantastic your offer is, almost guarantees that they will erase your email. Spending time drafting more inclusive emails is a quick approach to get rid of a huge roadblock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;2-findthe-most-effective-time&quot;&gt;2 Find the Most Effective Time&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider timing based on what you know about the person or what you’ve learned from your investigation. If you got the notion to contact this individual because they were just featured in a magazine, they’re undoubtedly getting a lot of pitches at the moment. Consider when that person’s inbox is less crowded, and when they are more likely to read and respond to your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;3-identify-the-decisive-individual&quot;&gt;3 Identify the Decisive Individual&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allow time to locate the appropriate point of contact. You don’t want to waste time investigating only to discover that you contacted the incorrect person and received no response. Utilize sites such as Linkedin to ascertain a person’s position inside an organization, and compose the email with an eye toward their issues and how you may assist them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;4-avoid-taking-up-too-much-space-in-someones-inbox&quot;&gt;4 Avoid Taking Up Too Much Space in Someone’s Inbox&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re communicating over email, keep it brief and direct. Make your request explicit and demonstrate how the person you’re contacting will benefit from replying. Because people’s inboxes are already clogged, it’s critical to demonstrate your worth. Additionally, attempt to customize your email. Individuals can recognize whether they are being spammed with a generic message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;5-run-numerous-subject-line-experiments&quot;&gt;5 Run Numerous Subject Line Experiments&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can have the best email in the world, but it will be ineffective if few people open it! We always experiment with different subject lines in order to increase our open rates, and the effort is well worth it. You’ll get the best results by customizing the subject lines based on an article or email they authored, a significant change they made to their website, or a recent mention in the press. Concentrate on those areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;6-launch-a-warm-up-email-campaign-for-cold-calls&quot;&gt;6 Launch a Warm-Up Email Campaign for Cold Calls&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send an email campaign to warm up your cold call outreach technique. Export the email campaign’s leads and target your cold call outreach precisely to those leads. Then export the leads who opened the email campaign and target this section for secondary outreach. Email campaigns and reporting data are excellent methods for marketers to connect the links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;7-research-three-levels-deep&quot;&gt;7 Research Three Levels Deep&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold outreach is based on the exchange of value. Consider the following framework while creating a cold pitch. The first level is defining your “ask.” The second level is defining the value you’ll provide if they express interest. Level three is all about defining the value you’ve previously supplied them with prior to delivering the first email. If you incorporate components from all three tiers into your introductory email, you will experience phenomenal success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;8-concentrate-on-the-location-industry-and-scale&quot;&gt;8 Concentrate on the location, industry, and scale&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our cold outreach is segmented by geography, industry, and company size. Contacting a local business always yields better outcomes. Industry type aids in the development of an engaging subject and material for an industry-specific project. The size of the business helps us determine the type of people we need to contact. Additionally, the combination of these criteria results in a reduced sample size that is easier to work with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;9-utilize-transcripts-of-sales-calls&quot;&gt;9 Utilize Transcripts of Sales Calls&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conduct analysis and evaluation of past cold calls to see what worked and how replies were perceived. Chorus.ai is an excellent tool for accomplishing this and for determining which words perform best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;10-approach-it-from-their-point-of-view&quot;&gt;10 Approach It From Their Point Of View&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than cold-contacting people for their business, think out how to give value to their life first. Bear in mind that individuals are primarily concerned with one thing: “What’s in it for me?” Ascertain that your outreach to prospective clients clearly communicates the level of value and assistance you wish to deliver. While this may seem obvious, surprisingly few cold outreach strategies adhere to this fundamental concept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;and-3-bonus-tips&quot;&gt;And 3 bonus tips!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;11-use-a-straightforward-closing-with-a-specific-reasonable-request&quot;&gt;11 Use a Straightforward Closing With a Specific, Reasonable Request&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bear in mind that the receiver receives a high volume of cold emails throughout the day, and many of them miss the mark when it comes to concluding the message. The seller either requests too much, too fast, or is ambiguous about what they want from the recipient. A straightforward conclusion that includes a specific and fair request, as well as flexible scheduling choices, goes a long way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;12-use-multiple-platforms&quot;&gt;12 Use multiple platforms&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of outreach techniques are platform-specific, such as email, phone calls, or direct mail. Utilize a service like FullContact to locate contacts across social media platforms, allowing you to establish a presence in many areas rather than relying just on phone calls or emails. Spread it out over time to avoid prospects feeling bombarded and “stalked.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;13-constantly-follow-up&quot;&gt;13 Constantly Follow Up&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personalizing your cold outreach email is no more a nice-to-have; it is absolutely necessary if you want to be noticed. However, many people overlook their initial try. Create an email series that will be automatically sent to your target individual every few days. This way, you’ll remain top-of-mind for them and boost your chances of being recognized.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html">Rather than cold-contacting people for their business, think out how to give value to their life first.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Emails With a Profile Photo in Gmail</title><link href="/article/news/how-to-add-your-brand-to-gmail.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emails With a Profile Photo in Gmail" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/news/how-to-add-your-brand-to-gmail</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/news/how-to-add-your-brand-to-gmail.html">&lt;p&gt;The Complete Guide to Displaying Your Profile Photo in Gmail&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interesting thing about Gmail is that when you send an email from your Gmail address (e.g. name@gmail.com), your Google account profile picture will appear next to your email address. However, you won’t see the Google Account profile picture when sending email using Gmail from a non-Gmail domain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m specifically talking about different email addresses set under “Send email as” in the “Accounts” and “Gmail import” settings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example like name@yourcompany.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;yourname@gmail.com &amp;lt;- Profile picture is displayed. 
name@yourcompany.com &amp;lt;- Profile picture is not displayed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk about boring!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where is the character?
If you get your branding right, you’ll want to be consistent across all social media channels, including Gmail. Sure, you might have a great custom signature line, but it shouldn’t end there.
Do you really want a blue people logo that represents your company in the email?
the new. That are great news. There is a very simple solution to showing your Google Account profile photo when sending email from a non-Gmail domain!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What’s my profile picture in my Google Account?” You asked?
This:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Profile picture of Gmail&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, you can completely modify this photo if you wish.
Here’s how to view your Google Account profile picture when sending email from a non-Gmail domain. Follow these steps to view your Google Gmail account profile picture when sending email from a non-Gmail domain. Example: Your domain is yourcompany.com and you can use Gmail to send email to name@yourcompany.com.
This is a quick and easy five-click process. It shouldn’t take more than three minutes. (Four or five cases for alcohol consumption or lack of sleep. Six minutes for both)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On your desktop / laptop, go to https://myaccount.google.com (or in Gmail, click your profile picture in the top right corner of the page, then click My Account).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On the left side of the page, click Personal Information.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Under CONTACT INFO, click on the arrow to the right of the email. Scroll down to a different email address.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Add your new / alternate / company to the alternate email cell. Note: If you can’t see the Alternate Email tab, you may need to click the Advanced button. There should be a “Legacy Email” section.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here you need to add all the email to your domain that you want to send from and view your Google account profile. Such as name@yourcompany.com.
You have to confirm the new email address by sending a confirmation email to the email address you added as an alternate email address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Check the new “Alternative” email when it hits your inbox. Do not skip this step as your profile picture will not appear until you do this.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To test, send an email to anyone with a Gmail email address. You should see your profile photo next to your name.
Like him:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ask the recipient to send you a screenshot of what they see to make sure it works.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html">The Complete Guide to Displaying Your Profile Photo in Gmail</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ideal client guide</title><link href="/article/news/how-to-improve-your-email-reputation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ideal client guide" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/news/how-to-improve-your-email-reputation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/news/how-to-improve-your-email-reputation.html">&lt;p&gt;With this guide, you can easily construct your cold email campaigns that get responses. Everyone who needs to reach out to someone they don’t know directly can profit from this e-book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-quick-and-dirty-guide-to-cold-emailing&quot;&gt;A Quick and Dirty Guide to Cold Emailing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold emailing is a vital sales and marketing tactic. This direct and bold approach can help many experts from many industries and niches, opening up new business and career chances. Let’s delve into the weeds of this evergreen technique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-thrive-at-cold-outreach&quot;&gt;How to thrive at cold outreach?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s review some basic guidelines to avoid having your cold emails marked as spam or garbage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Define your target market. This manner, you may tailor your copy to your recipients’ interests. In sales, building your Ideal Customer Profile is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do your homework. Cold email automation is essential for efficiency. But you must also be effective. So getting to know your recipients better will help you to target them more precisely. To learn more about folks you wish to cold email, use the internet, social media, and other means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Build your name and power. Your recipients will be more likely to open your cold email if they recognize your name. To advertise oneself, write blogs, hold webinars, use social media, and record podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get referrals. In your cold outreach, include names. A shared interest can help break the ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work on your topic line. The topic line is important. Attract your audience’s attention with fascinating content. It’s vital to A/B test your subject lines (and every other email element).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple is best. Today’s crowd is frantic. They don’t have time to read your life narrative, so keep it brief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Observe! Do it forever. Persistence (but not pushiness) is key to increasing open, click, and response rates. Expect no one who sees your name in their email to think you have something to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Observe, improve, repeat. Monitoring your cold outreach results will show you what works and what doesn’t. Learn HOW to improve your next cold email campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;define-your-audience&quot;&gt;Define Your Audience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding your target audience’s wants, preferences, and pain areas is critical to your outreach’s success.  By identifying your target market, you can tailor your pitch to their needs. But, how?  Here are some handy tips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ideal-client-type&quot;&gt;Ideal Client Type&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When starting a business, getting as many clients as possible is critical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The more prospects know about you, the better, but that doesn’t mean your marketing activities should be wide and broad.  You’ll waste time, money, and energy on the wrong opportunities if you try to do too much. In other words, you need to narrow your target and connect with fewer sales-worthy prospects.  Those are perfect customer profiles. These profiles of perfect-fit types of firms interested in purchasing your solutions should include the following information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry&lt;/strong&gt; it is self-explanatory why you should define your company’s sector or specialization. It’s best to start with one industry and then fine-tune as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Company size&lt;/strong&gt;, the number of employees, revenue, existing clients, or some other statistic can all be used to determine a company’s size.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location.&lt;/strong&gt; Knowing where your target customers are located is critical to understanding their needs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pain points​.&lt;/strong&gt; This is a crucial part to develop because knowing your prospective clients’ concerns will help you meet their demands and focus on the features of your product or service that will benefit them specifically.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How long this company has already been in business.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is the biggest reason they won’t buy your product? If your product is not usable by this particular company, try to find any impediments or unfavorable variables that could affect their decision to do business with you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is the key reason they should buy your product? Determine your product’s strengths and a unique selling feature that will appeal to the organization in question.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What can your product do for them?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;So, what goods or solutions are they using now to attain that goal?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These details help you focus your efforts on attracting, cultivating, and engaging organizations that fit the above description.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;buyer-personas&quot;&gt;Buyer Personas&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ideal customer persona is based on market research and real data about existing customers. It contains customer demographics, preferences, motivations, and goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A single ideal customer profile can have many buyer personas. They assist you understand your target audience’s qualities and motives, allowing you to better develop your marketing message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When creating buyer personas, identify their personal traits, values, story, and wants. Here are some questions to help you build your buyer personas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What does your buyer persona do? This helps you tailor your approach and know what to expect from your target audience. Establish a consumer persona’s education level, abilities, expertise, and professional interests to further refine the data.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What does your buyer persona do? How long do they work?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do they prefer email or phone communication? What social networking sites do they use? What stuff do they enjoy? What are their daily duties? The answers to these questions will help you choose the communication channel and build your marketing message.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Where do you live? Married or not? Is it a city? Apart from demographics, B2B organizations must incorporate organizational graphs in their buyer personas, indicating their industry, size, and department.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The main pain issues of your buyer persona? It’s also helpful to know what motivates them to hunt for a solution and how frustrated they are when they decide to buy from you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What influences your buyer persona’s decision-making process? Is it the product’s features and benefits that drive them, or is it urgency?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What do they see as common sales roadblocks? Is it your product’s pricing that’s out of their budget? Is their senior management unwilling to work with you?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Then what are their long-term goals? How can you help them? Make a plan to help your buyer persona achieve their goals and explain how your product may help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have your buyer personas, it’s time to prioritize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create a scale and rank your personas based on their alignment with your solution, budget, and organizational impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin contacting the highest ranked prospects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;segmentation&quot;&gt;Segmentation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many people may be interested in your products and services, their motives and reasons may vary greatly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You wouldn’t send the same message to a CEO and a manager, just as applying for two identical jobs necessitates different emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that your target audience can be separated into categories based on shared traits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can use the following six traits to segment your list and target your outreach:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**1. Location. **This is one of the simplest ways to segment your target market. If your business operates in multiple cities, states, or regions, it makes sense that you wouldn’t deliver the identical offer to customers in New York and Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re presenting your event online, don’t email your Canadian prospects that you’re hosting a conference in San Francisco. Your target audience will not pay much attention to your email since they will believe that what you say is irrelevant to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**2. Demographics. **Age, gender, income level, title, education level, industry, or corporate position can all be used to segment audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The more you know about your possibilities, the better. But finding so many details can be challenging because consumers dislike filling out forms when signing up for your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customer surveys can help you refine data about your prospects, but they only work if you reward them. Incentives will get you a lot of useful information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**3. New Subscribers. **Never undervalue new subscribers. Greeting them with a welcome email, or even better, an email sequence , will keep them warm and interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This strategy works well with various segmentation factors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**4. Past Purchases and Recommendations. **One of the most effective ways to segment your audience is by past purchases. Remind customers of upcoming refills or warranty expiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, automatic recommendations and reminders can be tremendous money producers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**5. Inactive Customers. **Not all clients who made one purchase or visited your website will return. A simple email inquiring why they stopped visiting your site or reminding them of the product or service they added to their shopping cart but never purchased is one way to reach this category and gain their attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social evidence, such as a product link with customer feedback, can be quite powerful here. If a subscriber hasn’t logged in for more than two months, ask if they still want to be a part of your community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disqualifying leads is as crucial as qualifying them in terms of keeping your list current and relevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**6. The Amount Spent. **While every penny counts, it’s still vital to segment your email list by wealth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you can’t offer a $1,000 item to someone who hasn’t spent $1,000 in your store. You can keep track of how different customers react to discounts, in addition to defining multiple price ranges and sending targeted communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically, high-end buyers prefer exclusive deals above discounts. However, discounts are important buying motivators for others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how hard you attempt to adapt and personalize your outreach, there’s still a chance you’ll run with some unsuitable prospects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stats show that 50% of your prospects don’t meet the criteria. Trying to cultivate them can squander time and money, as well as lose out on certain chances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;True, we usually discuss persistence as a key component of your outreach success. No matter how diligent you are, pursuing a bad loan will yield no results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Better to acknowledge your prospect is a dud early on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some red indicators to assist you identify and eliminate these incompatible prospects:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They miss scheduled meetings.&lt;/strong&gt; If this is an isolated incident, give them a chance. But if it’s a habit, stop it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They’re just looking.&lt;/strong&gt; You may either quietly tell them to contact you when they’re ready to buy, or you can continue to hope that they will buy from you after learning more about your product’s benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No real necessity.&lt;/strong&gt; If your prospect has the budget, authority, and desire for your product but lacks the need, they are unlikely to buy from you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No urgency.&lt;/strong&gt; If your prospect isn’t in a hurry and can’t explain why, you can assume they’re not in a hurry.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They don’t do homework.&lt;/strong&gt; If your prospect doesn’t execute the required tasks, they aren’t serious about buying.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No decision maker.&lt;/strong&gt; In other words, they’re hiding something and assessing their alternatives.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No price cut.&lt;/strong&gt; Is this happening before your prospect has fully grasped the value of your product?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They want insider information.&lt;/strong&gt; Your opponents may try to discover your plans. Be wary if your prospect asks plenty of inquiries but doesn’t reveal much about themselves.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They aren’t engaged.&lt;/strong&gt; If your prospect still doesn’t understand your product after a demo and all your resources, they aren’t engaged. The same goes for ambiguous messages and non-responsive decision-makers in their firm.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is no pain.&lt;/strong&gt; Some prospects’ quirks can harm your offer or complicate the entire process. Prospects that micromanage from the outset or are impossible to satisfy might be nightmares. Consider if you’re ready to work with them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html">With this guide, you can easily construct your cold email campaigns that get responses. Everyone who needs to reach out to someone they don’t know directly can profit from this e-book.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Warm Up Your Cold Email List and Increase Deliverability</title><link href="/article/news/how-to-warmup-your-cold-email-list.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Warm Up Your Cold Email List and Increase Deliverability" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/news/how-to-warmup-your-cold-email-list</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/news/how-to-warmup-your-cold-email-list.html">&lt;p&gt;Introduction: Why Cold Emails Fail &amp;amp; The Dos and Don’ts of Sending an Effective Cold Email&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;keywords: warm up your cold email list, cold email automation software, email marketing software&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s always hard sending an email to someone you don’t know, but the task becomes even harder when the person is not expecting it. That’s why cold emails fail. They are not sent at the right time or they are sent to people who are not interested in your offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s difficult to come up with an effective cold email list that includes people who would be interested in your offer or service, but luckily there are tools that can do it for you. You should find a software that automates this process, which will free up your time and allow you to send more emails without spending too much time on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold emails are still effective if they are well written and if they contain offers that people would want to take advantage of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay Away From These 10 Common Mistakes With Your Cold Email Campaigns
keywords: cold email mistakes, cold email automation, send personalized emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people don’t know how to create a cold email campaign, and this is why they make the mistakes that we will discuss in this section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We should avoid these 10 common mistakes with your cold email campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Having no clear goal: This is the most important thing when sending emails, and if you don’t have one, you are most likely wasting your time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Not sending personalized emails: It is always better to send personalized emails because it makes it easier for the recipient to open your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Sending too many emails at once: You should only send an email every 3 days or so because this will increase your click-through rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Not following up on unanswered emails: If you are not getting any replies after a few days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6 Tips for Emails That Are Guaranteed To Get Responses
keywords: warm up your cold email list, best practices for sending emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the rise of social media, cold emails have become increasingly less common in business communication. But when used correctly, they can be an effective way to introduce yourself and your company to potential customers. Here are some tips for optimizing your email outreach:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pick the right time of day: Emails seem more urgent in the morning and evening, so you’ll get a better response rate if you email people around those times.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Add a personal touch: Make it clear you’ve read their profile by mentioning something from it in your first sentence or two.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep your subject line concise: People will be more likely to open your email if they know what it is about from just reading the title of it, so don’t make them guess!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: The Benefits of Using Cold Email Automation Tools
The benefits of using a cold email automation tool are many. Whether you want to find new prospects, follow up with potential buyers, or keep contact with past customers, the right cold email automation tool can help you out. Here are some of the top reasons why you should use a cold email automation tool:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) It saves time and energy: There is no need to chase after potential buyers and send them one-by-one emails manually. The right software will do it for you and save your time and energy. 2) It improves sales: You can engage with your prospects more easily and encourage them to buy from you by sending them personalized messages which will improve your sales. 3) It’s easy to use: Cold email automation tools make it easier for non-technical people to manage their&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="news" /><summary type="html">Introduction: Why Cold Emails Fail &amp;amp; The Dos and Don’ts of Sending an Effective Cold Email</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications</title><link href="/article/test/long-term-profit-with-good-email-communications.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/article/test/long-term-profit-with-good-email-communications</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/test/long-term-profit-with-good-email-communications.html">&lt;p&gt;The Complete Guide to Creating a Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introduction: What is Good E-mail Communication and How Can it Help Your Business?
keywords: email communication, email etiquette, how to write an email&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E-mail is the most used tool for communication in our society. It’s easy to use, especially if you have an accepted template to follow. One of the most important things to keep in mind when composing an email is that it should be clear and concise. There are a few spelling mistakes to avoid when writing an e-mail because they might cause confusion and result in your message being ignored by the receiver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this section, we will cover different aspects of good e-mail communication and how it can help your business. We will also provide examples of bad email etiquette so that people can avoid them when composing their own emails, which would result in a higher response rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to Write Effective E-mails that Drive Conversions
keywords: how to write an effective email, how to open an email, what are the best types of emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An email is the way we convey messages to our audience. Every day, we receive emails from various sources, such as banks, retailers, and even social media sites. You may be surprised to know that the average person will spend over 80 hours reading and responding to emails this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want your messages to stand out in a crowded inbox, then it is important that you write an effective email that drives conversions. To help you do this, here are some best practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Open with a strong subject line&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use an appropriate greeting - Keep your messages short and concise&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Include a call to action&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject Line Strategies for Captivating your Readers Attention
keywords: subject line strategy, subject line tips, best practices for subject lines&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject line strategies are the first thing you see when you open your email inbox. It can make or break your email or conversion goals. A captivating subject line provides a glimpse of what’s inside and makes the reader curious to read more. But, how do we write those captivating lines?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best practices for subject lines are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Incorporate emotion in your subject line to grab the readers attention - Use action-oriented words to make readers want to take an action&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make it clear what they can expect from your email by using declarative statements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5 Tips for Writing Better Emails &amp;amp; Creating a Great Online Presence
keywords: tips for writing better emails, writing great emails online, 10 tips on writing good emails&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emails are a vital part of the modern office, and there are a few tips that you can follow to make sure that they’re written the best way possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep email communications simple&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use correct grammar and spelling&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Be concise&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Include a signature at the end of every email&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Proofread before sending&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: The Benefits of Good E-mail Communication and Why You Should Invest Time in It
In this section, we will discuss the benefits of good email communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email is one of the most common forms of communication from businesses from all over the world. There are many ways to use email to communicate with customers and employees, but a lot of people still don’t know how to do it properly or at a minimum they don’t know how to make sure that their emails are being read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This can be a huge problem for businesses because if their emails aren’t being read then they won’t have any new opportunities for customer interaction or for promotion. In order to be successful in communicating with customers through email, there are four tips that you should keep in mind: 1) Use Titles 2) Proofread Before Sending 3) Be&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="article" /><category term="test" /><summary type="html">The Complete Guide to Creating a Long-term Profit with Good Email Communications.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cold Email Templates</title><link href="/showcase/email/10-Cold-Email-Templates.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cold Email Templates" /><published>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</published><updated>2021-09-24T17:39:18+07:00</updated><id>/showcase/email/10-Cold-Email-Templates</id><content type="html" xml:base="/showcase/email/10-Cold-Email-Templates.html">&lt;p&gt;Some great showcases&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: https://www.klenty.com/cold-email-templates&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Foot in the door&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: The right direction, please?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi [First Name],&lt;br /&gt;
    Quick question: Who handles your team&apos;s &amp;#123;Department&amp;#125;?&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Competitors Name&amp;#125; is already using &amp;#123;Product&amp;#125; to &amp;#123;double revenue/reduce cost/improve productivity&amp;#125; and I don’t want your organization to miss out on this opportunity. &lt;br /&gt;
    However, I am not very sure who is the right person to make the most of this opportunity.&lt;br /&gt;
    If that’s you, then could you tell me how your calendar looks like this week? &lt;br /&gt;
    If not, would you be kind enough to point me to the person who would benefit the most from this conversation?&lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Word-of-mouth intro&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: &amp;#123;initial contact&amp;#125; told me to get in touch with you.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    I just had an exciting conversation with &amp;#123;initial contact&amp;#125;, who directed me to you.&lt;br /&gt;
    I noticed that &amp;#123;prospect company name&amp;#125; is being plagued by issues like &amp;#123;pain point 1&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;paint point 2&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;pain point 3&amp;#125;....&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Product name&amp;#125; can help solve these issues rapidly, and even &amp;#123;initial contact&amp;#125; strongly believes in it. &lt;br /&gt;
    However, he also pointed out that you are the person who can take a call on this and suggested we have a chat.&lt;br /&gt;
    Can we have a quick 5-10 minute call next week to explore our solution to these challenges?&lt;br /&gt;
    Shoot me an email, and I will fix a call at your convenience. &lt;br /&gt;
    Warm regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Getting past the gatekeeper&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Looking for the best [job area] contact&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    I am doing some research on &amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125; to determine if there is a need for [idea]. As a first step, I would like to have a call with someone from [job area] as it will help identify the fitment accurately.&lt;br /&gt;
    Could you navigate me to the best person at &amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125; for a brief discussion?&lt;br /&gt;
    Thank you,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Word-of-mouth intro&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: &amp;#123;Your organization&amp;#125; X &amp;#123;Prospect organization&amp;#125; = Perfect Fit!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
       
    Dear &amp;#123;first_name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
     
    My name is &amp;#123;your name&amp;#125;, and I’m with &amp;#123;your organization&amp;#125;. You were referred by &amp;#123;original contact&amp;#125; who thinks the fitment between &amp;#123;your organization&amp;#125; and &amp;#123;prospect organization&amp;#125; is great, and there are high chances of synergy if we work together. &lt;br /&gt;
     
    Did you know our product &amp;#123;product name&amp;#125; comes with &amp;#123;unique benefit&amp;#125;?&lt;br /&gt;
     
    Can we evaluate the possibility of a relationship between our organizations over a short call? &lt;br /&gt;
     
    Does Wednesday’s second half sound good to you?&lt;br /&gt;
     
    Kind regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Who is the right Person?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Implementing XYZ at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt; I am trying to figure out who is incharge of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;leading general statement&amp;#125;&amp;#125; there at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.  &lt;br /&gt; Would you mind pointing me towards the right person and the best way I might get in touch with them?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;value Proposition&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Result&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; We recently helped a start up &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert result&amp;#125;&amp;#125; by &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what you do&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.  &lt;br /&gt; Can you point me to the person who handles &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what you do&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to discuss further?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;WHO IS THE BEST PERSON?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Looking for best &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert job area where you’d like start&amp;#125;&amp;#125; contact&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;  I am doing some research on your company to determine if there is (or is not) a need for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert your strongest pain point&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;  Could you please help me by pointing me to the best person there for a brief discussion?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;OPEN WITH A COMPLIMENT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, you have an awesome website&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; I really like the clean design and usability of your website. It’s really, really good. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your brief value proposition&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and would like to speak with someone who is responsible for this area of your marketing, at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; Are you the right person to speak about this? If not, who do you recommend I should contact?  &lt;br /&gt;Many thanks,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;SYNERGIES&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Can you put me in touch with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;decision maker&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt; Was hoping that you might be able to introduce me to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;decision maker&amp;#125;&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;? I wanted to connect with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;him/her&amp;#125;&amp;#125; because our email lists target a similar demographic with limited overlap.  &lt;br /&gt;Seeing our products are non-competitive, I wanted to touch base to see if &amp;#123;&amp;#123;he/she&amp;#125;&amp;#125; was up for brainstorming ways to leverage our existing user bases to grow both of our lists. &lt;br /&gt; We did this with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125; in the past, and both parties received a 15% lift in new subscribers.Any help is much appreciated.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;SCALING CUSTOMER ACQUISITION&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, reduce your cost per acquisition&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;  One of our clients was able to acquire about 6,000 customers at half of their target cost per acquisition number.  &lt;br /&gt;Is this something that might interest you right now? &lt;br /&gt; If so, can you point me in the direction of the person that handles this?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;CONNECTING BASED ON ONLINE PROFILE&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, need your help!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;  My name is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;my name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and I head up business development efforts with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;my company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. We recently launched a new platform that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;one sentence pitch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; I am taking an educated stab in the dark here, however, based on your online profile, you appear to be an appropriate person to connect with … or might at least point me in the right direction.  &lt;br /&gt;I’d like to speak with someone from &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; who is responsible for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;handling something that’s relevant to my product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. If that’s you, are you open to a fifteen-minute call on _________ &amp;#123;&amp;#123;time and date&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to discuss ways the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; platform can specifically help your business? &lt;br /&gt; If not you, can you please put me in touch with the right person? I appreciate the help! Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;the elevator pitch&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Scaling Customer Acquisition&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; One of our clients was able to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;improve metric by number&amp;#125;&amp;#125; at half of their target cost per acquisition number. Is this something that might interest you right now? &lt;br /&gt; If so, can you point me in the direction of the person that handles this?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;I LOOKED AT YOUR SITE&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, thinking of engagement metrics?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; This is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I just took a quick look at your site and noticed that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; looks similar to many of the SaaS clients that we help every day. &lt;br /&gt; I’m sure you’re already thinking about engagement metrics and ROI by acquisition source, but I’d love to get a sense for how you’re uncovering that data and share some insights we’ve learned along the way towards understanding the story behind your business. &lt;br /&gt; If I’ve got the right person, can we connect in the next few days? If not, who would you recommend I speak with?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;GOOD FIT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;+&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; will be a good fit&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; I hope this note finds you well.I’ve been working for a company called &amp;#123;&amp;#123;my company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; that specializes in X, Y and Z. In thinking about your role at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I thought there might be a good fit for your group. &lt;br /&gt; Our &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; has garnered a lot of attention in the marketplace and I think it’s something that your organization might see immediate value in.Can you help me get in contact with the right decision-maker?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;With a BLURB&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Introduction to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;contact name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; It was fantastic meeting you last week at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;event&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I enjoyed our conversation about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic discussed&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; As we were discussing what I’m working on, you mentioned that you know &amp;#123;&amp;#123;contact name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; over at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;s/he&amp;#125;&amp;#125;’s an expert in this space.  &lt;br /&gt;If you’re willing, an introduction to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;contact name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; would be greatly beneficial and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;s/he&amp;#125;&amp;#125; might be interested in learning more.I understand you might have a lot going on so I attached a short blurb below to make the introduction as easy as possible. Would you be able to take a moment to introduce me?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Favorite Team&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Build a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;department&amp;#125;&amp;#125; team like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;favourite team&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,  &lt;br /&gt; I see that you’re a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;team&amp;#125;&amp;#125; fan, so you must be excited about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;player&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;player’s achievement&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; As &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; continues to scale, your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;department&amp;#125;&amp;#125; team needs &amp;#123;&amp;#123;pain point that you solve for&amp;#125;&amp;#125; just as &amp;#123;&amp;#123;how same point applies to team&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. We’re the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;player&amp;#125;&amp;#125; of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;industry/market niche&amp;#125;&amp;#125;…&amp;#123;&amp;#123;funny comparison&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I’d love (if possible) to be referred to the best person on your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;department&amp;#125;&amp;#125; team to introduce &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; as a mean to hit your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Vision Alignment&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: &amp;#123;Your organization&amp;#125; &amp;lt;&amp;gt; &amp;#123;Prospect’s Company&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;
      Wanted to reach out and introduce myself.&lt;br /&gt;
      I am John, and I work as an AE and &amp;#123;Company name&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
      Our company’s product &amp;#123;product name&amp;#125; helps businesses solve &amp;#123;pain point&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;
      I just wanted to check with you what your vision is for &amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125; and how we could help you align with that vision. &lt;br /&gt;
      Let me know what your calendar looks like, and I would be happy to set something up. 
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Thanks, &lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The compliment Intro&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Time to talk?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
      I recently visited your LinkedIn profile and couldn’t help noticing that you have been promoted as &amp;#123;Prospect position&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;Prospect company&amp;#125;. Congrats! &lt;br /&gt;
      I also understand that in this position, you must be acquainted with all the processes related to &amp;#123;department&amp;#125; in your organization.&lt;br /&gt;
      Do you think that &amp;#123;prospect’s organization&amp;#125;’s operational efficiency can be improved through &amp;#123;idea&amp;#125;?&lt;br /&gt;
      If so, our solution should be definitely attractive to you.&lt;br /&gt;
      Are you available next week for a quick call on this subject?
      Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Specificity +  Customer Story&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Achieve &amp;#123;Goal&amp;#125; in &amp;#123;Timeframe&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
      I have an idea that I can explain in 10 minutes. This will help &amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125; achieve &amp;#123;goal&amp;#125; in &amp;#123;time frame&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Another customer&amp;#125; who used &amp;#123;Product name&amp;#125; was able to achieve this in &amp;#123;time frame&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; 
      Would you be interested to know how it happened?&lt;br /&gt;
      If yes, let me know a good time this week for a quick chat.&lt;br /&gt;
      Best,&lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Showcasing curiosity&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Loved your product!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;
      I found your organization on LinkedIn and think your product is fantastic. Your vision - &amp;#123;company vision &amp;#125; on your website intrigued me so much that I decided to reach out with a proposal. &lt;br /&gt;
      How would you feel if we can help &amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125; achieve that vision while you handle other mission-critical activities? &lt;br /&gt;
      Here’s an interesting read on how &amp;#123;your company&amp;#125; can achieve that - &amp;#123;Link to blog/case study/whitepaper&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;
      Do you have 15 min to discuss this further?  &lt;br /&gt;
      If yes, feel free to book a meeting with me by clicking here. &lt;br /&gt;
      Thanks! &lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Mutual connection&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;mutual connection&amp;#125;&amp;#125; recommended we get in touch&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Mutual connection&amp;#125;&amp;#125; recommended we get in touch. I work for a company called &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; that does &amp;#123;&amp;#123;XYZ&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; In thinking about your role at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I thought there might be a great fit for your group. &lt;br /&gt;Our [product name] has been extremely well-received in the marketplace and I think it’s something that might be helpful for you!&lt;br /&gt; Do you have time to chat next week?&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;trigger based outreach&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Congrats! Have you thought of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;business value&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Since I work so much with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your targeted industry&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I constantly follow industry news. I’ve noticed that you recently &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company action&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Congrats!&lt;br /&gt; Usually when that happens, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;business value&amp;#125;&amp;#125; becomes a priority. That’s why I thought you might be interested in finding out how we helped &amp;#123;&amp;#123;similar company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; get going quickly in their new direction – without any of the typical glitches.&lt;br /&gt; If you’d like to learn more, let’s set up a quick call. How does &amp;#123;&amp;#123;specific day and time&amp;#125;&amp;#125; look on your calendar?&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Ideas for you&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: A few ideas: How can you improve sales?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; My name is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and we work with companies like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company names&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to improve their sales. &lt;br /&gt;I’ve already started looking at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and I have a few ideas about how you can drastically increase your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;type of sales&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. For example, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;how you can help with existing issue&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I have a lot more ideas that may be useful for you. Do you have time on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Date and Time&amp;#125;&amp;#125; for a 15-minute Hangout or Skype call?&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Resort to Outright Flattery&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: It’s finally great to connect with a sales legend&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I have to say this right off the bat: I really admire the work you’ve done at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and how you’ve improved &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what they’ve done&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I would love to pick your brain on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;their specific skill&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I think you can continue to increase those sales with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your services&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Time is precious but I wouldn’t as if there wasn’t some substantial benefit for you. Can I steal you away for a 15-minute phone call tomorrow at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert time&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;br /&gt; Thanks,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;LinkedIn article&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Great Article - &amp;#123;&amp;#123;LinkedIn Article name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; The article you shared on LinkedIn yesterday addresses a challenge that I’ve heard two sales directions mention this week.&lt;br /&gt; Your unique perspective would be beneficial for them to hear. We help sales execs improve their reps success with a similar approach. Do you have 5 mins to speak on Wednesday or Thursday afternoon this week? &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;General Truth&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Value Proposition in brief&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; from &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; here.&lt;br /&gt; Companies make more sales with consistent marketing. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; can put proven sales tools into the hands of everyone who sells your product.&lt;br /&gt; If that sound useful, I can explain how it works.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;LEARN ABOUT YOU&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub:&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; + &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; My name is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.We help &amp;#123;&amp;#123;specific company type&amp;#125;&amp;#125; with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;one liner&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I wanted to learn how you handle &amp;#123;&amp;#123;thing your company handles&amp;#125;&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and show you what we’re working on.Are you available for a brief call at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;time options&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;USE NUMBERS AND STATS&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Are you up for a 70% increase in your top-line revenue?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;What would it mean to your top-line revenue if you saw a 70% increase in contact rates, 50% improvement in closes, and 40% increase in quota-hitting sales reps?&lt;br /&gt; Let’s find a few minutes to talk about how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is providing these results to our clients. &lt;br /&gt;I’m available tomorrow &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert 2 times you’re available&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Can we sync up?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Quick call&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: 10x &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; traction in 10 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I have an idea that I can explain in 10 minutes that can get &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; its next 100 best customers. &lt;br /&gt;I recently used this idea to help our client &amp;#123;&amp;#123;SaaS company/competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125; almost triple their monthly run rate. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;let’s schedule a quick 10-minute call so I can share the idea with you. When works best for you?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;ANALYSIS ON YOUR PRODUCT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub:&amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, increase your revenue by x%&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I really like what you’ve done so far with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and we genuinely believe it has a great potential. &lt;br /&gt;Earlier this week we’ve basically done an analysis with a new product that we recently launched and found that you have an easy 15% revenue improvements. &lt;br /&gt;We were a bit surprised as the average result that we get with similar websites is around 9%.&lt;br /&gt; I’d really like to give you a quick call sometime next week to show you the results and get your opinion.Let me know your thoughts.Thanks,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;FOCUS ON BENEFITS&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Value Proposition in brief&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; In working with other &amp;#123;&amp;#123;INSERT INDUSTRY OR POSITION&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, one of the key issues they’re struggling with is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;INSERT KEY ISSUE&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.This past year we helped numerous companies to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;INSERT BUSINESS DRIVER&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, resulting &amp;#123;&amp;#123;MONEY SAVED, REVENUE ADDED, PRODUCTIVITY INCREASES&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;If this is something you’re challenged with too, let’s set up a quick call. I have some ideas that might help.&lt;br /&gt; All the best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;TALK DOWN YOUR COMPETITION?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub:What do you think of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your competitor’s product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Just ran across your website and noticed you were using &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your competitor’s product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.How are you liking it?I run a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;service&amp;#125;&amp;#125; called &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; It’s just like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your competitor’s product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, only &amp;#123;&amp;#123;key differentiator&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. If you’re up for it, I would love to jump on a quick call with you and get your opinion on how we could make &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; better (and see if it would make sense for us to work together).&lt;br /&gt; Would &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert 2 times&amp;#125;&amp;#125; be a good time for you?(if not, I’m flexible, just let me know)
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;HEAD TO HEAD AGAINST YOUR COMPETITOR&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;NAME&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Are you liking &amp;#123;&amp;#123;competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Just ran across your website and noticed you were using &amp;#123;&amp;#123;COMPETITOR NAME&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; How are you liking it?I run a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;SERVICE&amp;#125;&amp;#125; called &amp;#123;&amp;#123;YOUR COMPANY NAME&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. It’s just like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;COMPETITOR&amp;#125;&amp;#125; only &amp;#123;&amp;#123;SHORT DIFFERENTIATOR&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. If you’re up for it, I would love to jump on a quick call with you and get your opinion on how we could make &amp;#123;&amp;#123;COMPANY NAME&amp;#125;&amp;#125; better (and see if it would make sense for us to work together).&lt;br /&gt; Would &amp;#123;&amp;#123;TIME OPTIONS&amp;#125;&amp;#125; be a good time for you?(if not, I’m flexible, just let me know)
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Help us...HELP YOU&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub:Can we help you achieve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;&amp;#125; too?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;In working with other &amp;#123;&amp;#123;job title&amp;#125;&amp;#125;s, one of the key issues they’re struggling with is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;key issue&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; This past year we helped numerous companies to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;business driver&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, resulting &amp;#123;&amp;#123;money saved, revenue added, productivity increases&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; If this is something you’re challenged with too, let’s set up a quick call. I have some ideas that might help.&lt;br /&gt; All the best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;PERSONALIZED DEMO&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Check out this personalized demo for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I love &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and I’m also a big fan of your blog.I work with companies like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s competitors&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and help them &amp;#123;&amp;#123;key benefits&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;Here’s an example of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;give an example&amp;#125;. Just wanted to email you and see if &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; might be interested in a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;similar type of solution&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I made a demo for you based on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what it was based on&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to show you what it might look like. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;paste the demo attachment&amp;#125;&amp;#125; Is this something you guys would be interested in?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;BE UPFRONT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Revenue Growth&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; My name is &amp;#123;your name&amp;#125; and I’m with &amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;, a [what you do]. &lt;br /&gt;We’ve worked with venture-backed startups to Fortune 500 companies like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;companies you’ve worked with&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;We take a different approach to growing companies and aren’t like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;other companies in a competitive niche&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;We move quickly and if we don’t think we can kick butt for you, we’ll be upfront about it.Are you free for a chat this week or next about marketing? If so, I’ll be available at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert two times&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;SAW YOUR CAREERS PAGE&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Hiring &amp;#123;&amp;#123;title of your end users&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I noticed on your careers page that you’re hiring &amp;#123;&amp;#123;title of your end users&amp;#125;&amp;#125; who &amp;#123;&amp;#123;describe the problem&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Would love a few minutes to discuss how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; removes this burden.&amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; helps clients like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s competitors&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;solution&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;List some benefits&amp;#125;&amp;#125;Would you be open to a call &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert two times&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to see how we could help your team?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;COMPETITOR JUST DID X&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect’s Competitor&amp;#125;’s &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Trigger Event&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I’m sure you heard &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect’s competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125; recently &amp;#123;&amp;#123;trigger event&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.I think now would be the perfect time to make a move to take some market share from them.&lt;br /&gt; They’re probably really busy with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;trigger event&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and aren’t thinking as much about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;category your product/service is in&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I have some ideas how you could take advantage and achieve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;broad benefit&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Do you have 5 minutes tomorrow morning to chat?&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;TRIGGER EVENT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Trigger Event&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I’m reaching out because &amp;#123;&amp;#123;trigger event — hiring new person dealing with vendors of the category you’re in&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;I know sometimes that causes people to want to switch &amp;#123;&amp;#123;service you provide&amp;#125;&amp;#125; vendors to get &amp;#123;&amp;#123;benefit&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;I wanted to see if you would like to make more informed decisions quicker. If this is of interest to you, can you please let me know either way?&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;BE A SUPERSTAR&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Be a superstar like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idol&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Based upon your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;social media&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, you’re a fan of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idol&amp;#125;&amp;#125; – inspiring me to reach out to you here.&lt;br /&gt; What would &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idol&amp;#125;&amp;#125; be without &amp;#123;point of relation&amp;#125;? &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Funny commentary&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;My company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idol&amp;#125;&amp;#125; of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;industry or market niche&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Our platform provides &amp;#123;&amp;#123;benefit 1&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;benefit 2&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Features like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;feature 1&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;feature 2&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;feature 3&amp;#125;&amp;#125; make your team &amp;#123;&amp;#123;benefit 2&amp;#125;&amp;#125; – making them ready to boost their fame (much like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idol&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and their team). &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; – might you be willing to connect for just a few minutes to talk about how we can get your team onto &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idol&amp;#125;&amp;#125;’s level?&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;NEW BLOG CONTENT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Your feature on my blog body&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I&apos;ve been a fan of what you&apos;ve been doing with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; over the past couple of years.&lt;br /&gt; I&apos;m reaching out because I&apos;m working on a new piece geared towards &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic of the blog post you&apos;re writing&amp;#125;&amp;#125; from those who&apos;ve already been through this experience themselves and I&apos;d love to hear your take on it.&lt;br /&gt; The post will be publishing to my blog &amp;#123;&amp;#123;optional—that gets x # of readers&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and I&apos;d love to get a quick quote from you to include in the piece if you&apos;re up for it. &lt;br /&gt;If you&apos;d be able to answer this question in a few sentences, that would be amazing:&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Relevant question/challenge that will give them an opportunity to showcase their expertise&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; How do you advise people on overcoming that challenge? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;LOVED THE ARTICLE&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Service&amp;#125;&amp;#125; (and mention)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I wanted to reach out and give you a heads up that I&apos;ve been loving the &amp;#123;your service medium&amp;#125; coming out of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; these past few months.&lt;br /&gt; I can appreciate great &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your service medium&amp;#125;&amp;#125; when I see it 🙂Just shared your recent &amp;#123;post, project, design, rebranding work, app, etc&amp;#125; about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;xyz&amp;#125;&amp;#125; with my audience on Twitter and I also mentioned the platform as a great resource in one of my recent blog posts &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;The other reason I&apos;m reaching out is because a large part of my business is working with brands like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;reference any relevant past clients or even full-time gigs&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and others to help scale &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your core service offering&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;Would you be up for chatting about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&apos;s&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your core service offering&amp;#125;&amp;#125;? &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; P.S.&lt;br /&gt; Here&apos;s where you can read more &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link to portfolio page if possible&amp;#125;&amp;#125; about my process and the clients I&apos;ve worked with
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;DEMO VIDEO FOR YOUR BLOG&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, a free demo video for your blog&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I am huge &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; fan. I especially liked your recent video on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;abc&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I take keen interest in making videos and work with companies like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and make weekly video&apos;s for their blog.&lt;br /&gt; Here is a video that was published last week on their site - &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link url&amp;#125;&amp;#125; Would &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; be interested in a similar series? I have made a demo for you to get an idea of what it will look like.&lt;br /&gt; Check the video here &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link url&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Just say the word and I will set up a meeting to discuss the finer details.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;USING COMMON CONNECTIONS&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Interview for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your blog post&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your tweeting my blog post &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link url&amp;#125;&amp;#125; mentioning you. I am overwhelmed.I am actually working on an another similar blog post &amp;#123;&amp;#123;idea/topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;The basic idea of this blog post is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your value proposition&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I wanted to see if I can grab 5-10 mins of your time to talk about experiences that I can share with my readers.&lt;br /&gt; Let me know if you are interested and I will set up the call.&lt;br /&gt; Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;PS: Here&apos;s me quoting our mutual friend &amp;#123;&amp;#123;ABC&amp;#125;&amp;#125; in Forbes &amp;#123;&amp;#123;url link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;PPS: Here&apos;s a piece that I wrote for Inc featuring your buddy &amp;#123;&amp;#123;XYZ&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt; PPPS: I love tacos just like you, so I am can&apos;t be a bad guy!
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Writing to an influencer&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, you are so awesome!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Hope you are doing great. I have been a big fan of yours since I saw you speak at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;some event&amp;#125;&amp;#125; about how you turned down a $xxxxxx job offer at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;some company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to start your own company with $yyyyy in your bank account and grow it to where you are today...it was so inspiring.&lt;br /&gt; I was wondering if you will be interested in being a headline speaker at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your conference&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, an annual startup conference for B2B startup founders.&lt;br /&gt; You can set up a recruiting booth at the event if &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect&apos;s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is hiring or just spread the Marini gospel, but I will do whatever it takes to make speaking at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your conference&amp;#125;&amp;#125; worth your time and easy for you.&lt;br /&gt; I can give you a more in depth run down if you had like: here is a gist if it &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link url&amp;#125;&amp;#125; Best, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Reaching out to prospect&apos;s who use your competitor&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Alternative to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Competitor name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Just ran across your website and I notice that you are using &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.How are you liking it? We have built a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;service you provide&amp;#125;&amp;#125; called &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; It is similar to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125; but only more simpler and powerful to use.&lt;br /&gt; If you are up for it, I would love to jump on a quick call to get your opinion on how we can improve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and check if it makes sense for us to work together.&lt;br /&gt; Would &amp;#123;&amp;#123;date and time&amp;#125;&amp;#125; be a good time for a call? (If not, I am flexible. Just give me buzz anytime) Thanks,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Favourite article&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Title of the favourite article&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I was searching for some articles about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and I came across this page on your blog &amp;#123;&amp;#123;url link&amp;#125;&amp;#125;I noticed that you linked to one of my favourite articles &amp;#123;&amp;#123;title of the topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I reference this post a lot.Just wanted to give you a heads up that I published something similar. &lt;br /&gt;It is like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;repeat title of the topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125; but more thorough and up to date.&lt;br /&gt; Here is the link to my article &amp;#123;&amp;#123;title - url link&amp;#125;&amp;#125;I&apos;d love to hear your feedback on it. Also might be a worth to mention on your page?Either way, keep up the awesome work. Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;If you want to connect with the buyer&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Are you doubling down on &amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I came across &amp;#123;&amp;#125;&amp;#123;prospect&apos;s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; recently and was going through your website and thinking how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect&apos;s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; can really accelerate sales and lead generation. &lt;br /&gt;I did a quick search and found over 16,000 people on Linkedin with the title &amp;#123;&amp;#123;designation&amp;#125;&amp;#125; in the US alone. &lt;br /&gt; Imagine that you can find a super easy way to: &lt;br /&gt;1. Collate a list of these &amp;#123;&amp;#123;designation&amp;#125;&amp;#125; who are potential prospects for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect&apos;s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;2. Find accurate contact information for these prospects and &lt;br /&gt;3. Reach out to them in a personalised and targeted manner to talk about how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect&apos;s company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; can help themWell, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is a tool that can help you solve the 3 challenges outlined above to deliver new prospects on a consistent basis.&lt;br /&gt; If that sounds useful, would you be interested in a quick call/ or a free trial to help you get started?&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Reaching out to your niche market&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Elementary, my dear &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; “Data. Data. Data. I cannot make bricks without clay.” Sherlock Holmes said it about detective work.&lt;br /&gt; But it fits for sales too. If you know exactly who to reach, when to reach them and the little things about who they are, then all you need to do is click &apos;Send&apos;. &lt;br /&gt;I see that you sell to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;industry&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. At &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, we specialize in that very vertical and can get you the prospects that you are most likely to convert. &lt;br /&gt;How about a quick call to talk more? Can I block 15 minutes on your calendar sometime this week? &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Loved the article&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Re: Loved your article about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125; - here&apos;s my results&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I have been following your blog post for the past 3 years, so many great insights. &lt;br /&gt;Your recent post on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;post title/topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125; really resonated with me, I followed it step and step and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;brief on how the article was helpful for you&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I have written a post about it here &amp;#123;&amp;#123;url link&amp;#125;&amp;#125;If you are so inclined, I&apos;d love for you to share it with your audience.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;I JUST MET YOU EMAIL&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, it was nice to meet you&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; It was nice to meet you at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Occasion where you met&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I loved learning more about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;!Something discussed&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I’m really interested to learn more about your role as &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Job title&amp;#125;&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, as &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Reason why you’re interested&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; If you have time in the coming weeks, I’d love to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Follow up action&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and hear more about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Something you’d like to ask about&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Glad to meet you,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Poach Competitor&apos;s Customer&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company X&amp;#125;&amp;#125; acquires &amp;#123;&amp;#123;competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125; - keep using all the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;X features&amp;#125;&amp;#125; you love&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;As you may have heard, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company X&amp;#125;&amp;#125; acquires &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Competitor&amp;#125;&amp;#125;​​​​​​​. Sometimes acquisitions work out and sometimes ... the product gets shut down.&lt;br /&gt; Or starts drifting from its vision. Or the new owners increase its price by a lot.​​​​​​​Over at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, we have all the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;X features&amp;#125;&amp;#125; you love:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Feature 1&lt;br /&gt; 2. Feature 2&lt;br /&gt; 3. Feature 3 &lt;br /&gt;Plus, we can do a lot more to 10X your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;1. Benefit 1 &lt;br /&gt;2. Benefit 2 &lt;br /&gt;3. Benefit 3 &lt;br /&gt;Give us a try. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Link url&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Regards &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;THE REFERRAL WARMUP&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Contributing to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; (&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Connection&amp;#125;&amp;#125; referral)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I&apos;ve been loving the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;relevant (true) complement based on the work in your discipline&amp;#125;&amp;#125; coming out of the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; for the past few months, especially the recent &amp;#123;&amp;#123;relevant post, design, rebrand, feature, update and a quick note showing you actually looked at it&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;One of my acquaintances, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;name of connection&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is a contributor to the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and she recommended I reach out to you to see if it&apos;d be a good fit for me to contribute as well.&lt;br /&gt; Right now, I typically &amp;#123;&amp;#123;one liner about the services you offer and niche that it&apos;s in, showing your clearly a good potential hire for them&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;If possible, add an extra sentence highlighting relevant past work or offering up more industry credibility boosters.&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; Let me know if this sounds interesting and I&apos;d be happy to put together a few ideas on a &amp;#123;&amp;#123;deliverable&amp;#125;&amp;#125; we can test out!&lt;br /&gt; Regards
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Trigger Event + Common Connection&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Congrats on X, connection to Y&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;LinkedIn description, company’s recognition in the Inc. 500, connection with XYZ colleague&amp;#125;&amp;#125; inspired me to reach out. &lt;br /&gt;Other staffing firms like A, B, and C leverage &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to accomplish X and Y.Within six months of working with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, client &amp;#123;&amp;#123;saw X results&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I’d be happy to share a few ideas about how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; could accomplish the same.If you’re open to it, when would be a convenient time to chat? Say, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;XYZ time&amp;#125;&amp;#125;? &lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;RAINMAKERS&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, your thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Based on what we&apos;re seeing with other sales organizations, your sales reps are most likely wasting X-Y% of their day searching or creating marketing content.&lt;br /&gt; That means significant hours spent away from core selling activities.Automatically push proven, winning content to reps at the right time during the sales cycle. &lt;br /&gt;Your sales and marketing peers report this cuts ramp up in half and helps under-performing reps share relevant content like your &quot;rainmakers&quot;. &lt;br /&gt;To see if &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is worth a deeper dive, when would you have 15 minutes to learn more?&lt;br /&gt; Thanks in advance,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Outreach for a guest post&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, loved your awesome post!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I loved the post that you published last week on your blog about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;…that definitely puts words to a feeling I’ve had, yet haven&apos;t articulated. &lt;br /&gt;Just shared it on my Twitter &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link url&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and it’s gotten a couple of RT’s already :-) &lt;br /&gt;Totally tangent, but I write on similar topics for companies like x,y and z and would like actually love to contribute one article for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; blog.&lt;br /&gt; Would you recommend recommend that I try reaching out to for kickstarting that conversation?&lt;br /&gt; Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Mutual Interest&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: &amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;, You might find this super-useful&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello, &lt;br /&gt;
      Your latest post on LinkedIn about &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125; got me thinking. &lt;br /&gt;   
      I found this &amp;#123;article/video/post&amp;#125; that might help you in your further research.  &lt;br /&gt;
      Here’s the link to read it: &amp;#123;URL&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;  
      Hope you find it helpful. &lt;br /&gt;
      Regards, &lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Expert value addition&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Saw you attending &amp;#123;event name&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;,
&lt;br /&gt;
      Because I work so much with &amp;#123;target industry&amp;#125;, I constantly follow its news. Recently I noticed that you attended &amp;#123;event&amp;#125; in &amp;#123;city&amp;#125;.
      &lt;br /&gt;
      It helped me understand that you are passionate about &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;. That’s why I thought of sending you this list(attached) of other similar events happening in &amp;#123;city&amp;#125;.
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Hope to meet you at one of these events.
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Content-based authority building&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;,
&lt;br /&gt;
      Let me take a moment to introduce myself. I&apos;m &amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;Job Role&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;Company&amp;#125;. Our company has been the market leader for more than &amp;#123;X Years&amp;#125; in the &amp;#123;industry&amp;#125; industry.
      &lt;br /&gt; 
      I can see that you are very keen on &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125; from your recent blogs, hence thought of getting in touch with you to share our company’s articles on the same topic. 
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Here is the link to access them - &amp;#123;URL&amp;#125; 
      &lt;br /&gt;
      If you need any more information, please feel free to get back to me, and I will do my best to get you the necessary information.
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Case study email&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: &amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;, I just found this treasure&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;first name&amp;#125;,
&lt;br /&gt;
      I just received this awesome case study in my inbox today that revolves around &amp;#123;prospect industry&amp;#125;.
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Here is a quick summary of this case study - 
      &amp;#123;Summary&amp;#125;
      &lt;br /&gt;
      If you’re interested, I also have a few ideas that we can build on top of this case study that will be quite useful to your business.
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Are you available for a quick call tomorrow? If yes, what time works?
      &lt;br /&gt;
      Thanks, &lt;br /&gt;
      &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Sharing a Blog Post&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Blog Post Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I’m just writing to let you know that our latest post, about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what your blog post is about&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;In it, I share &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what it’s about&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. As a digital marketer, I believe it will be very valuable to you.&lt;br /&gt; Here’s a link to the latest post: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Post link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; I hope you enjoy it and I’d love to hear your thoughts on it. All the best. &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Sharing Resources&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Resources&amp;#125;&amp;#125; for you.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; We founded our business back in &amp;#123;&amp;#123;date of founding&amp;#125;&amp;#125; which means that we’ve had a lot of time to learn the ins and out of &amp;#123;&amp;#123;type of business you’re in&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I wanted to use this as a time to shoot you some ideas that you could implement in your business. I’ve compiled a document of resources including tests that we’ve run on our website and blog posts containing information about our business that will hopefully give you the inspiration you need to get started on the right foot.&lt;br /&gt; You can find those resources here: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Link to resources&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; Cheers, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Recommend a Tool&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Have you tried using &amp;#123;&amp;#123;tool&amp;#125;&amp;#125; for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I came across your tweet recently on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;problem you are facing&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Have you tried using &amp;#123;&amp;#123;recommendation&amp;#125;&amp;#125;? I use that with my team and it has been incredibly successful.&lt;br /&gt; Happy to chat more about it or send over some templates and examples if you’re interested.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Visited Website&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Want to talk more about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I noticed that you and some of your colleagues at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;their company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; visited our website and downloaded a white paper on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I was wondering whether you were trying to learn more about how you might improve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;business solution&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. So, I would be happy to setup a no strings attached 30 minute consultation with our expert team on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Let me know if you think this might be useful? Hope to hear from you. Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Additional Resources&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Here are some resources for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I’m just writing to let you know that our latest post, about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what your blog post is about&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. In it, I share &amp;#123;&amp;#123;what it’s about&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; As a digital marketer, I believe it will be very valuable to you.&lt;br /&gt; Here’s a link to the latest post: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Post link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; I hope you enjoy it and I’d love to hear your thoughts on it. All the best. &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Responding to an online post&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Ideas for generating leads&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt; I saw that you recently posted a question on LinkedIn about how to generate new leads for your company. &lt;br /&gt;I’ve found that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;solution&amp;#125;&amp;#125; has been successful for several companies in your space. I would love to set up some time to chat about this solution if it strikes your interest.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Helpful resources&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, more resources for you&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt; I noticed that you recently visited our &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Page or Blog Post&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I wanted to quickly check in and make sure that you were able to find the resource you were looking for? &lt;br /&gt;I also thought you might find these additional resources helpful:&lt;br /&gt; – &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link to helpful resource&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;– &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link to helpful resource&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;I actually also took a minute to look at your company, and I thought you might be interested in how your current performance compares to the industry benchmarks that we regularly see. &lt;br /&gt;Would you like to talk tomorrow at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert 2 times you’re available&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;A presentation&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Your site isn&apos;t optimized!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I noticed that your blog/site isn&apos;t optimized for mobile! Here is how you can improve it: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;share the visual presentation&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; has a plugin that can easily optimize wordpress blogs/sites to enhance the reading experience of your readers on phones and tablets.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;We would love to connect over the phone for few minutes and get this fixed for you.&lt;br /&gt; Alternatively, you can also download our plugin here &amp;#123;&amp;#123;url link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;GAMIFICATION&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Idea to gamify &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;’s sales team&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I’d like to share a quick idea with you that has helped &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Clients&amp;#125;&amp;#125; gamify their sales team and exceed their revenue goals.The concept is fairly simple, and leverages the game mechanics of competitions like Fantasy Football, and has powerful results.&lt;br /&gt; When can we have a quick call so I can explain? &lt;br /&gt;Thanks,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;INDUSTRY/COMPETITOR EVENT&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Saw the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;recent industry/competitor event&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I saw that the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;new industry event&amp;#125;&amp;#125; will result in &amp;#123;&amp;#123;negative effect for the company&apos;s revenue&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I think our company may be able to help you deal with the situation. With &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, you should be able to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your value proposition&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;Should we talk or is there someone else that I can connect with for a quick 15-20 minutes call?Our company &amp;#123;&amp;#123;name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, helps &amp;#123;&amp;#123;brief about the pain point your product/offering will resolve&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; We have helped other companies &amp;#123;&amp;#123;companies list&amp;#125;&amp;#125; increase their revenue by x% in just 3 months.&lt;br /&gt; Are you or someone from the team available to hop on a quick call sometime over the next week or two?&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;If you&apos;re a stranger to them&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: 26 seconds (or less)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;I&apos;ll keep this short and sweet to make the 26 seconds it takes to read this worth your time (yes, I timed it.)As a &amp;#123;job title&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I get to speak with people like you about &amp;#123;achieving X&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect&apos;s company&amp;#125; &amp;#125;is on my radar because we&apos;ve helped a lot of companies in &amp;#123;&amp;#123;industry/space&amp;#125;&amp;#125; with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;business area&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Could we schedule a 15 to 20 minute call to discuss your strategy for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;achieving X&amp;#125;&amp;#125; -- what excites you, which challenges you see, and how you envision your plan changing down the road? &lt;br /&gt;Even if you decide not to continue the conversation after our call, you&apos;ll leave with some advice for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;business area&amp;#125;&amp;#125; that will make an immediate impact.&lt;br /&gt; Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Access to Research Report&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, impressed with your growth rate!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; Your quarterly report shows an impressive growth rate, especially at your scale. &lt;br /&gt; Fast growth companies like &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; usually dedicate significant resources towards &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your area of expertise&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. We have some market research that shows how companies allocate resources to different parts of the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;expert area&amp;#125;&amp;#125; process.&lt;br /&gt; Would you be interested in seeing the research report, so you can benchmark yourself?&lt;br /&gt; Regards, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Reason-based pitch&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Remember me?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi,&lt;br /&gt;
    I hope you &amp;amp; your family are safe.&lt;br /&gt;
    You might have received a mail from me a week ago regarding &amp;#123;Product name&amp;#125;.
    Our customers, many of whom are in the &amp;#123;industry&amp;#125; sector, have successfully solved their  &amp;#123;pain points&amp;#125; through &amp;#123;product name&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
    Here are three compelling reasons why you should consider it for&amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt;
    Reason 1&lt;br /&gt;
    Reason 2&lt;br /&gt;
    Reason 3&lt;br /&gt;
    If you would like us to help attain &amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;, do send a short ‘Yes’, and I will take it forward from there.&lt;br /&gt;
    Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Routine follow-up&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Did you miss my last mail???&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;firstName&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    Just following up on my last message as there is a good chance that you missed it in the barrage of emails you receive every day.&lt;br /&gt;
    I am still hoping to jump on a quick call with you to understand any challenges that &amp;#123;Company Name&amp;#125; is facing and to see if &amp;#123;product name&amp;#125; can assist in any way.&lt;br /&gt;
    Are you free early next week for a quick call?&lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Information Injection&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Do you want more information?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;

    I trust that you had an opportunity to read my previous emails and take a peek at our website. &lt;br /&gt;
    So I figured it’d be worth checking in with you again. &lt;br /&gt;
    Have you given any additional thought to &amp;#123;product&amp;#125;? &lt;br /&gt;
    I’d be happy to set up a quick call so that I can clarify any queries you may have on it.&lt;br /&gt;
    What day of the week would suit you for a quick conversation? &lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks, &lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Contextual follow-up&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Still hoping to connect with you &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;
    I’m sorry we haven’t been able to connect.  &lt;br /&gt;
    When we last spoke, you seemed very interested in [product name].  &lt;br /&gt;
    In all probability, you must be incredibly busy to not respond after our initial chats.
    I am happy to schedule a call with you any time this week, even if it falls outside our regular office hours or on a weekend(if that makes it easier for you).  &lt;br /&gt;
    I really don’t mean to be persistent with you, but I would appreciate some indication of your decision either way.  &lt;br /&gt;
    Looking forward to your response. &lt;br /&gt;
    Kind Regards, &lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Simple follow up&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; again. Just touching base from few weeks ago. &lt;br /&gt;Would love to have a quick conversation to see if I could you help you with your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;give a solution to their problem&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;Are you available &amp;#123;&amp;#123;insert two times&amp;#125;&amp;#125; for a quick 10 minute call? &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Confidence + Empathy&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Challenge&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I understand your position, but I wouldn’t follow up with you if I didn’t strongly think that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; can help &amp;#123;&amp;#123;their company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; solve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;challenge #1&amp;#125;&amp;#125; by &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product benefit #1&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product benefit #2&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;I can promise you that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is going to be an industry standard. By choosing to not implement it, you’re putting your business and your ability as a &amp;#123;their department&amp;#125; person at a disadvantage. &lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you want me to jump on a call so I can walk you through what we do. &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Early follow up&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Let’s take another look&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Last we chatted, you requested that I get in touch in November. I may be a month early, but I figured it’d be worth checking-in. &lt;br /&gt;Have you given any additional thought to my proposal? I’d be happy to do a quick review of it on the phone and answer any pending questions. &lt;br /&gt;What does your calendar look like to talk? &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Post voicemail&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Sorry, I just missed you&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I just called to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;explain your purpose&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;In my voicemail, I mentioned that I’ll try you again on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;date and time&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, but feel free to reach me whenever works best for you at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;phone number&amp;#125;&amp;#125; or shoot me any questions via email. &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Offer to help&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Drop me a note if you caught this &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Would love to chat some more about your sales / provide any assistance I can there. Discussing your plans for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your area of expertise&amp;#125;&amp;#125; (even if it’s just advice I can pass on!) would be great too. &lt;br /&gt;Hope you’re having an excellent start to the week.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;For a busy prospect&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Drop me a note if you caught the email below &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;; I know you’re a busy man! &lt;br /&gt;I’d love to talk a little bit more about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, yourself, and any ways in which we can be collaborating. A phone call / Skype would be a pleasure.&lt;br /&gt; Hope you had an excellent weekend.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;ONE STEP AT A TIME&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub:Next Step?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I’m writing to follow up. I’m not sure what our next step is.Let me know what makes sense as a next step, if any?&lt;br /&gt; Thanks for your input.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;BTW WE WERE IN THE NEWS&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; we got some new press coverage &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; that I wanted to share with you. I’d love to pick up on our conversation. When’s a good time to chat?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;DIDN&apos;T HEAR BACK&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I didn’t hear back from you last week when I was looking for the appropriate person managing your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;statement&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;That’s not a problem.If it makes sense to talk, let me know how your calendar looks.If not, who is the appropriate person?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Follow up and ask for referral&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I have tried to get in touch with you to see if there is a mutual fit between our companies expertise and your goals around &amp;#123;&amp;#123;statement&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;If you are not interested or there is another person you would like me to follow up with, please let me know. &lt;br /&gt;Would it make sense to invest 5-10 minutes to determine if there is a mutual fit between your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;statement&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and our expertise?If not, who do you recommend I talk to?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;JUST MISSED YOU&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I just missed you!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Must have just missed you! I just left a voice mail on your cell.Please shoot me an email or call me when you get a chance at (xxx xxx xxx)looking forward to connecting.&lt;br /&gt; Best Regards
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;When waiting for an answer&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Same subject&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;!First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; In case you missed my email &amp;#123;&amp;#123;!week/day you sent it&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &amp;#123;&amp;#123;restate why you’re reaching out&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Value statement specific to recipient&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; My ask for you:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First part of ask&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Second part of ask&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Any additional information&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Looking forward to your reply,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Social proof&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Same subject&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;!First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I wouldn&apos;t be reaching out again but I strongly think that we can work together and we can help you &amp;#123;&amp;#125;&amp;#123;achieve goal&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Freshtrip, Intercom and Autopilot, three of the fastest growing SAAS startups in the bay area use us &amp;#123;&amp;#123;core benefit of your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; every day. &lt;br /&gt;I suspect that we could be helpful for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; as well. Can we schedule some time to talk this week? &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Testimonials&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, you will love us like others do&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;!First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Incase you are still on the fence about whether automated prospecting makes sense for you, I wanted to share a few quotes on what our customers are saying about us:&lt;br /&gt; “&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is now the backbone of our sales prospecting process” – VP Demand Gen at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;CompanyName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, a leading digital marketing firm &lt;br /&gt;“The prospector works like a charm and integrates beautifully with our CRM to keep all data in sync &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Customer&amp;#125;&amp;#125;” – VP Sales at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Customer Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; Intrigued why so many sales people love to use &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your Product Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;? We should talk!&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Ask for a meeting&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Free for a coffee? On me!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I am going to embarrassingly honest: I&apos;ve really enjoyed learning more about what you do and would love the opportunity to connect over coffee to learn more about your experience with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;industry&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt; I am currently doing &amp;#123;&amp;#123;role&amp;#125;&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, and am very interested in learning more about how you use A/B testing to enhance &amp;#123;&amp;#123;detail from last conversation&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I know you must be very busy, so thought it might be a good idea to catch you when you step out for a coffee this Wednesday or Thursday at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;time&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. The coffee is on me. Just let me know!&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Interest-based value&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Here’s an interesting read&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    I didn’t hear back from you for a while. &lt;br /&gt;
    During this gap, I read a blog that I found extremely interesting.&lt;br /&gt;
    Here’s the link &amp;#123;URL&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
    Hope you find it as interesting as I did.&lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Importance-based value&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Heard this in &amp;#123;event&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    Recently, I attended &amp;#123;event&amp;#125; where &amp;#123;name of the speaker&amp;#125; spoke about &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
    I understand &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125; is of primary importance to you and your organization.&lt;br /&gt;
    I captured all the important notes and have converted them into a doc (attached herewith).&lt;br /&gt;
    Hope you find it useful.&lt;br /&gt;
    Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Solution-based value&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: This &amp;#123;Blog/case study&amp;#125; on &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125; could be a great value add to you...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi [First Name],&lt;br /&gt;
    When I got hold of this &amp;#123;Blog/case study/whitepaper&amp;#125; on &amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;, I got reminded of your recent speech at the &amp;#123;event&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;
    I felt this would be a great value add for your business and hence thought of sharing it with you.&lt;br /&gt;
    Do not hesitate if you need more such resources from my end. I would be happy to help.&lt;br /&gt;
    Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Post Event, In depth&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Will this convince you?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;company name&amp;#125; team, &lt;br /&gt;
    Typically when I haven’t heard back from someone, it means they are either swamped or aren’t interested in our offerings presently.&lt;br /&gt;
    If it is the latter, is there anything that I can do to make you consider us for &amp;#123;solution&amp;#125;?
    How about this case study which explains the scenario where we helped &amp;#123;another company&amp;#125; to achieve &amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
    Link to access case study- &amp;#123;URL&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt;
    Let me know if you need additional details about this case study or any other information in general.&lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Post Event, In depth&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Excited about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;event&amp;#125;&amp;#125; at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I’m sure improving your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;objective&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is a top priority for you. I thought I’d send you &amp;#123;&amp;#123;piece of content&amp;#125;&amp;#125; for you to go through. In this post, we discuss the 5 key ways of improving your &amp;#123;&amp;#123;objective&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;Would love to know if &amp;#123;&amp;#123;piece of content&amp;#125;&amp;#125; was helpful to you. Let me know if you would like to discuss this in greater detail over a call.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Educate Your Prospect&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Key challenges in implementing &amp;#123;xyz&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Following my previous email on how we can help &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; implement &amp;#123;&amp;#123;xyz&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I wanted to share this &amp;#123;&amp;#123;piece of content&amp;#125;&amp;#125; that talks about the key challenges companies face in this context.&lt;br /&gt; Let me know if you have any questions about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. I would love to get on a call to discuss this in greater detail.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Share something + follow up&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Can we hop on a quick call Wednesday 4pm or Thursday 11am?&lt;br /&gt; Cheers,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; PS: thought you might find this article interesting &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Final Email+Last in series&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Over the past couple of weeks, I’ve sent you a series of emails that I hope have been valuable to you. This is the final email you’ll be receiving as a part of the series. &lt;br /&gt;If you’ve been enjoying the emails I’ve been sending, then I’ve got one more thing I’d like to share that I think you’ll find useful:&lt;br /&gt; Our &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, which we built to help &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your target audiences&amp;#125;&amp;#125; deliver(s) &amp;#123;&amp;#123;the thing that you sell&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; If you’re struggling to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;first thing your product will fix&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, or feel overwhelmed by &amp;#123;&amp;#123;second problem your product will fix&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I encourage you to give us a try.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;This is where you will say the length of your free-trial and what is required to sign up&amp;#125;&amp;#125; You can try it free here: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;link to your free trial&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy, and once again, welcome to the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; community &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;If you just called them&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; -- just gave you a ring&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Saw that you were checking out our &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, and wanted to give you a quick shout after checking out the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; site. &lt;br /&gt;The last thing I want to do is waste your time or mine, but I thought it would be helpful to quickly speak and learn a bit more about what you hope to get from &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and share some best practices.&lt;br /&gt; Most of our successful users will have a quick set up like this to get things started in the right direction.&lt;br /&gt; Is there a good time for you today or the next few days? You can book some time directly on my calendar here: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Meetings link&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Best, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; P.S. Thought you might like this as well while getting started:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Helpful link #1&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Helpful link #2&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;USING FREE OR TRIAL VERSION&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: What&apos;s next?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;How are you finding &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; so far now that you&apos;ve tested it pretty well? &lt;br /&gt;You&apos;ve locked down the basics of getting &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; to work for you - A, B , C. A few tips I thought you might find useful.&lt;br /&gt; - Tip 1 &lt;br /&gt;- Tip 2 &lt;br /&gt;- Tip 3 &lt;br /&gt;I&apos;d love to hear how we&apos;re meeting your expectations. If there&apos;s anything that you haven&apos;t found compatible yet, do let me know. &lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Prospects gone dark&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Are we meant for each other?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;But it still stings :( Sounds like we weren&apos;t meant for each other. But I wanted to reach out to you one last time. &lt;br /&gt;I have a few suggestions on how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; can &amp;#123;&amp;#123;accomplish X and Y&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. If I don&apos;t hear back, I&apos;ll assume that the timing isn&apos;t right. &lt;br /&gt;In the meantime, here are two &amp;#123;&amp;#123;links, resources&amp;#125;&amp;#125; I thought you might &amp;#123;&amp;#123;enjoy, find value in&amp;#125;&amp;#125; because &amp;#123;&amp;#123;reason why they&apos;re relevant&amp;#125;&amp;#125;:&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Link #1&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Link #2&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;If they opened your email but never replied&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Resources used by &amp;#123;&amp;#123;comp_1&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;comp_2&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; Following on my previous email, as they have a tendency to slip through the cracks. &lt;br /&gt;At the very least, I wanted to provide you with the top resources that your peers at other &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect&apos;s industry&amp;#125;&amp;#125; companies found helpful: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Helpful link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Case study&amp;#125;&amp;#125; Would it be helpful if we scheduled 15-20 minutes to discuss how some of these topics may align with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect company&apos;s&amp;#125;&amp;#125; 2017 strategy?&lt;br /&gt; Just book some time on my calendar here: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Meetings link&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Product Updates&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, quick update from &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Hope all is well. &lt;br /&gt;Last time we spoke you didn&apos;t think that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; was a not a goof fit for your needs because &amp;#123;&amp;#123;reason why they didn&apos;t close&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;The good news is that we now &amp;#123;&amp;#123;new feature which addresses their concern&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Based on our past conversations, I think we are in a better position to help you to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;achieve X by doing Y&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Just say the word and we will set up a trial account for you and your team. &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Personal detail&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: I just ordered &amp;#123;favorite drink&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;firstName&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    I know that your time is valuable, so I reached out to &amp;#123;prospect’s teammate&amp;#125; from your team to know what&apos;s your favorite drink is in the morning...&lt;br /&gt;
    Guess what I&apos;m holding in my hand right now? &lt;br /&gt;
    Yes, it is &amp;#123;favorite drink&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Image of favorite drink&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt;
    Let me know which day suits you so that we can share a drink and discuss the possibility of working together in the future.&lt;br /&gt;
    Best,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt; Information request context&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: I hate sales emails too! &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;
    Yes, I’m sending you one right now, but in my defense, it’s because you requested more information on &amp;#123;solution&amp;#125;.  &lt;br /&gt;
    If you’re really not interested in achieving &amp;#123;goal&amp;#125;, please let me know so I can stop being such a hypocrite.  &lt;br /&gt;
    Seriously, every time I click “Send,” it hurts me a little bit. Help stop my suffering and please find a suitable time on my calendar here. &lt;br /&gt;
    Regards &lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Life betterment email&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Life Is Great :)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello! Hello!&lt;br /&gt;
    The sun is shining, the birds are chirping, and you know exactly how to solve &amp;#123;pain point&amp;#125;. Right?&lt;br /&gt;
    If you&apos;re still working on that last one, which I know can be a real pain in the back,  I&apos;d love to offer some world-class strategies that I&apos;ve shared with your friends (read: competitors). &lt;br /&gt;
    Please feel free to book some time on my calendar if you want to sprint ahead of your friends (I know you do). &lt;br /&gt;
    Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Playful email&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;&amp;#123;Name&amp;#125;, Do you like Puzzles?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi,&lt;br /&gt;
    L_T&apos;_ CH_T T_IS W__K&lt;br /&gt;
    Were you able to successfully fill in my puzzle? The correct answer is - &quot;Let&apos;s Chat This Week.&quot;  (drumroll :)&lt;br /&gt;
    I know you&apos;re busy, but I&apos;d love to have the opportunity to show you how &amp;#123;product name&amp;#125; can help you solve &amp;#123;pain point&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
    Please feel free to book some time with me here: [Insert Meetings link]&lt;br /&gt;
    And if we have time, we can solve more puzzles after the call :)&lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
    
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The Super Hero&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I’ve reached out a few times regarding your sales prospecting strategies there at &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. My guess is that we’re out of touch for one of three reasons: &lt;br /&gt;– You don’t see a fit &lt;br /&gt;– You have another solution to create predictable outbound prospecting numbers &lt;br /&gt;– You are secretly a superhero and have been too busy fighting crime to reply &lt;br /&gt;If any of these are correct then they may be the exact reason why we should talk now… &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The T-Rex one&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Are you ok?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt; I reached out previously regarding &amp;#123;&amp;#123;WHAT YOU DO&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and haven’t heard back from you yet. &lt;br /&gt;This tells me a few things: &lt;br /&gt;• You’re being chased by a T-rex and haven’t had time to respond. &lt;br /&gt;• You’re interested but haven’t had time to respond. &lt;br /&gt;• You aren’t interested. &lt;br /&gt;Whichever one it is, please let us know as we’re getting worried! &lt;br /&gt;Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;NEW CHAPTER&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: C-H-A-N-G-E-S&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;I’ve reached out to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; several times over the past few weeks. What I talked about clearly didn’t resonate.&lt;br /&gt; I heard the collective yawn and have made some changes. &lt;br /&gt;This partnership is now about three simple things:Helping you improve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;X area of business&amp;#125;&amp;#125; Helping you solve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;X challenge&amp;#125;&amp;#125; Helping you achieve [X results]If the above sounds interesting, let&apos;s connect so I can provide more information on how we have started a new chapter.&lt;br /&gt; Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;ADELE&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Hello from the other side&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hello &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I must have called a thousand times ...On a more serious note, last time we talked about &amp;#123;&amp;#123;pain&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and how &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; could help &amp;#123;&amp;#123;drive X results/accomplish X goal&amp;#125;&amp;#125; over &amp;#123;&amp;#123;specific timeframe&amp;#125;&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; Are you still interested in continuing our discussion? If not, please let me know so I can stop being Adele.&lt;br /&gt; Cheers, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The Blunt Ask&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, how do we proceed?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt; I&apos;m in salesman hell a.k.a &quot;Radio Silence&quot; &lt;br /&gt;I have officially stalked you via phone, and now I thought I&apos;d try emailing you.&lt;br /&gt; How would you like me to proceed? &lt;br /&gt;1. Keep calling you &lt;br /&gt;2. Email you every two days &lt;br /&gt;3. Take the opportunity out of the pipeline &lt;br /&gt;Just reply the option number.&lt;br /&gt; Thankfully,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Comment on your Blog Post&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, thanks for your comment&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;Thank you for the lovely comment for my article on &amp;#123;&amp;#123;topic&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. Glad that it helped you solve &amp;#123;&amp;#123;problem x&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. &lt;br /&gt;Just remember, we are always an email away if you need help. (Well, help with our app. I have no clue about good vacation spots in Alaska.) &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;‘Next steps’ email &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Is it time to part ways?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;
    I’m writing to follow up on my previous email. Do you think you still might be interested in our &amp;#123;product&amp;#125;?&lt;br /&gt;
    If you still are, what do you recommend as the next steps? If not, could I reach out to you in a couple of months?&lt;br /&gt;
    Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Wrong timing email&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Perhaps the timing just isn’t right?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123; First Name&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt;

    I wanted to reach out to you one last time regarding &amp;#123;value proposition&amp;#125;.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    If I don’t hear back from you this time, I’ll assume that the timing isn’t right, and I won’t contact you again.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    However, If you&apos;d still like to learn how &amp;#123;Your Company&amp;#125; can help you reach &amp;#123;goals&amp;#125;, feel free to book time on my calendar, and I will be happy to help.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    Goodbye for now!
    &lt;br /&gt;
    Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Empathy breakup&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Trying to connect &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi [Name],&lt;br /&gt;
    I know how hectic things can sometimes get while trying to balance work and personal life.
    Probably that’s the reason why I’ve never heard back from you after our last call. &lt;br /&gt;
    If that’s not the case, then it could only mean you are not interested in our offerings. 
    Either way, I will not be bothering you again with my emails. &lt;br /&gt;
    However, you can send me an email anytime if you change your mind about partnering with us.
    Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The Silence Breaker&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Subject: Hope I was of value to you&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;
    We’ve spent a good deal of time together, and I learned a lot from you. Hope you were able to get some value out of our conversations. &lt;br /&gt;
    From your silence for the past few weeks, I am assuming you are no longer interested in getting associated with us for solving &amp;#123;pain point&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt;
    If that’s the case, it is best that I close your file. If I am wrong in my assumption, send me a short reply and I will walk you through the next steps.&lt;br /&gt;
    Kind Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
    &amp;#123;Your Name&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Closing the File&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Permission to Close Your File&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; We are in the process of closing files for the month. Typically when I haven’t heard back from someone it means they’re either really busy or aren’t interested.&lt;br /&gt; If you aren’t interested, do I have your permission to close your file?&lt;br /&gt; If you’re still interested, what do you recommend as a next step? &lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your help. &lt;br /&gt;Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Courteous and Firm&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Thanks from &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I know we haven’t been able to connect, which usually means one of two things: Either the timing may not be right or you no longer have a need.&lt;br /&gt; In either case, I want to respect your time so I’m going to go ahead and close your file.&lt;br /&gt; Otherwise, if you would still like to talk, let me know a good time.Thanks again.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;one line zinger&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Re: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Client company name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; + &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt;Any interest here or is it time for me to hang up the towel?&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The professional breakup&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Thanks from &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; I wanted to reach out to you one more time regarding &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Subject Matter&amp;#125;&amp;#125;. If I don’t hear back from you, I’ll assume that the timing isn’t right and I won’t contact you again. &lt;br /&gt; If I can be of assistance, you can always contact me at the number in my signature.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The QUASI Breakup&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject used in first touch&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First Name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, Okay, &lt;br /&gt; I get it. It sounds like it’s not the best timing right now. &lt;br /&gt; However, I’m convinced that &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your product&amp;#125;&amp;#125; is something that is going to help your business be even more successful. &lt;br /&gt; That’s why I’ve included some examples (include 2-3 case studies) of how &amp;#123;your product&amp;#125; can help you &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product benefit #1&amp;#125;&amp;#125; and &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product benefit #2&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, and I’ll touch base in a month or so to update you on what’s new.&lt;br /&gt; Best,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Corny Subject line&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Is the love gone?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, I wanted to reach out to you one last time. I have a few suggestions on how your company can improve in terms of [metric]. If I don’t hear back from you, I’ll assume the timing isn’t right.&lt;br /&gt; My information is below should you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;THE CLASSY BREAKUP&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: RE: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;same subject&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; Haven’t heard back from you. Thank you for the opportunity. Can I put it on hold for now?
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;1,2,3. That&apos;s it&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Should I stay or should I go?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, &lt;br /&gt; I know you’re busy. Just give me a 1, 2, or 3&lt;br /&gt; 1. We’ll pass on partnering with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;this year, thanks for the offer! &lt;br /&gt; 2. We’re interested in the &amp;#123;&amp;#123;product&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, but it’s not a good time, reach back out to me in 1 month.&lt;br /&gt;  3. I’m interested — let’s talk! &lt;br /&gt; Thanks!
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The Polite Ask&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: Is &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; the best fit for &amp;#123;&amp;#123;prospect company&amp;#125;&amp;#125;?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;FirstName&amp;#125;&amp;#125;,&lt;br /&gt; We are always working on ways to improve, and conversations with prospective clients like you are essential to the success of our business.&lt;br /&gt; I recently spoke to you about our product and we seemed to be a good fit for your needs. But since then my attempts to reach you have failed.&lt;br /&gt; No matter the reason for the halt in communication, I hope that you would fell comfortable telling me if we are not a fit.&lt;br /&gt; Let me know if this is still an opportunity that you are interested in pursuing? If not, I completely understand and wish you all the best.&lt;br /&gt; Regards,
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;The Last Email&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, would love your feedback&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hey &amp;#123;&amp;#123;First name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt; This is my last email, but I&apos;d love your feedback so our product can get better. &lt;br /&gt; What&apos;s the main reason you didn&apos;t want to hop on a call with us? &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect first name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt; Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Appreciate your feedback&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;, quick favour&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;&lt;br /&gt;  Thanks for taking the time to &amp;#123;&amp;#123;talk to me about/consider/download a trial of&amp;#125;&amp;#125; product X. I understand if it’s not a fit and &amp;#123;wish you the best with Y opportunity, hope you find a solution to Z problem&amp;#125;.&lt;br /&gt; I’m sure you’ve got a lot going on, but if you have a minute, would you mind telling me which two or three things would’ve changed your mind?&lt;br /&gt; I’m always trying to improve and would really appreciate the feedback.&lt;br /&gt; Best,&lt;br /&gt; &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  
 
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-title&quot;&gt;Priority Focussed Break up&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-sub-title&quot;&gt;Sub: My Last Attempt Unless You Want to Reconnect&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;template-head-box&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&quot;template-body-copy&quot;&gt;
      Hi &amp;#123;&amp;#123;Prospect name&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt; I&apos;ve reached out to you a few times recently to reconnect and I haven&apos;t heard back from you. I understand that you&apos;re busy, so if exploring a partnership with &amp;#123;&amp;#123;your company&amp;#125;&amp;#125; isn&apos;t a priority, please let me know so I can stop bothering you. However, when we spoke last, you mentioned a few key areas that you were looking to improve:&lt;br /&gt; 1. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;VALUE PROP #1&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;2. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;VALUE PROP #2&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt;3. &amp;#123;&amp;#123;VALUE PROP #3, etc&amp;#125;&amp;#125; &lt;br /&gt; Are these still priorities for you? If I don&apos;t hear back from you then I&apos;ll assume this isn&apos;t the right time to continue our conversations and that something changed since we last spoke. &lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#123;&amp;#123;Your name&amp;#125;&amp;#125;
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="showcase" /><category term="email" /><summary type="html">Some great showcases</summary></entry></feed>